♪ Pokémon, I'll catch you! ♪
♪ (Pokemon Getto da ze-!)  ♪
Subbed by Vulpix500
Edited and spellchecked by malachitez
♪ be it in fire, water, grass, forests ♪
Tatoe hi no naka Mizu no naka Kusa no naka Mori no naka ♪
♪ the grass, the ground even under that girl's skirt (eakkk!!) ♪
♪ Tsuchi no naka Kumo no naka Ano ko no sukaato no naka (Kya~!) ♪
♪ it is very, very, very, very difficult to handle ♪
♪ Nakanaka nakanaka taihen da kedo ♪
♪ but I will catch them ♪
♪ Kanarazu GET da ze! ♪
♪ I'll catch Pokémon! ♪
♪ Pokemon GET da ze!! ♪
♪ Masara town, to you, I say bye-bye ♪
♪ Masarataun ni sayonara bai-bai ♪
♪ I'm going on a journey, with this guy (Pikachu) ♪
♪ Ore wa koitsu to tabi ni deru (Pikachuu!) ♪
♪ I'll win every battle with the moves I've mastered ♪
♪ Kitaeta waza de kachimakuri ♪
♪ then head to the next town with the friends I've made ♪
♪ Nakama wo fuyashite tsugi no machi e ♪
♪ there is no way to guarantee ♪
♪ Itsu mo itsu demo umaku yuku nante  ♪
♪ that everything will go as planned (that's right!) ♪
♪ Hoshou wa doko ni mo nai kedo (Sorya sou ja!) ♪
♪ but there's some that will always live honestly ♪
♪ Itsu demo itsu mo honki de ikite 'ru ♪
♪ these guys! ♪
♪ Koitsu-tachi ga iru  ♪
ah, I want to be a Pokémon master so bad ♪
♪  Aa Akogare no pokemon masutaa ni ♪
♪ I want to be one, I must be one ♪
♪ Naritai na Naranakucha  ♪
♪ I will become one! ♪
♪ Zettai natte yaru---!  ♪
and now! nidorino's horn strike!
Gengar dodges it brilliantly!
And now, Gengar's hypnosis
this render's Nidorino useless!
It fell asleep!
oh? The trainer has returned Nidorino.
What will they bring out next?
It’s Iwark
It takes advantage of it's huge body—
What’s this now? It used tackle!
Gengar dodged it. Gengar moves well
That's right, I'm Satoshi!
This young boy is 10 year old Satoshi.
In Masara town, where he lives
When I turn 10, I get my Pokémon licence..
From the town's Pokémon researcher, Professor Okido
You will get a starter Pokémon
I'm setting out on a journey to become a Pokémon Trainer.
That's right, I declare to the Pokémon of the whole world
I'll be the best Pokémon trainer
No, a Pokémon master,
that's what I'll be!
How long have you been awake, Satoshi?
11:00 p.m. is adult time.
Tomorrow is the day I start my journey
I can't sleep.
If you can't sleep, study.
Masara Town Pokémon Education Course for Beginners
The first Pokémon I want to recommend is
Fushidane,
Hitokage,
or, Zenigame.
Whoever the trainer chooses has its strengths and weaknesses.
When this finishes, go to bed immediately.
I know.
And make sure to change into your pajamas!
Pokémon! I choose you!
Fushidane is easy to grow and perfect for beginners
Fushidane, I chose you!
Ah... wait
Zenigame
Zenigame, I choose you!
I'll go with this
but wait,
Hitokage is recommended for new trainers with diffrent tastes
Hitokage, I chose you!
Huh? The sun is out?
Zenigame, Fushidane, Hitokage. Any will do, just wait for me!
Good, good, Shigeru, do your best, do your best, Shigeru
Good, good, Shigeru
Sorry! Comming through!
Oh... I'm sorry.
Geez! That hurts!
Oh? are you Satoshi?
Yes, yes, you are Satoshi
Satoshi, late from the beginning?
Shigeru
It's "Shigeru-kun" add the "kun"
But you’re late today
As my rival, you're already screwed from the beginning
So your first Pokémon is...
Get it right and it's inside this monster ball
Good, good, good, Shigeru!
thank you my friends and girlfriends
I'm sure I’ll become a Pokémon Master
And spread the name of this town, Masara Town, to the world!
Shigeru-kun
yes?
what kind of Pokémon did you get?
I have no obligation to tell you
After all, I'm the grandson of
Pokémon researcher, Professor Okido.
With the name of Grandpa,
I've got a decent Pokémon
Everyone who see's me off,
thank you for your hard work.
I, Shigeru, am a
Pokémon trainer from now on
I'm off!
Ah... Rival
Huh? Isn't it Satoshi?
Oh, Professor Okido, who's my Pokémon?
Your Pokémon?
Yes, my Pokémon
Come to think of it, I heard there were four people scheduled for today...
But the boy is going to training in his pajamas?
Pajamas get in the way
I was careless and late, but I'm not a boy.
I'm a 10 year old boy
which means, it’s time for my Pokémon!
I've been hesitating for a long
time, but I've already decided Zenigame
I choose you as my Pokémon!
Huh?
It was taken by a child who was not late
Ah... it's my fault for being late
Then it's Fushidane, that's my Pokémon!
The child who came on time took it too
Heh...
Alright, I choose you Hitokage
You are the Pokémon I choose!
Wha...
For trainers, or even Pokémon, a one second delay can change your life
So, I start without a Pokémon?
I do have another one...
I'll take that one!
This remaining Pokémon has...
It has a problem
It's also a problem with me being late.
Alright then!
This Pokémon is called Pikachu.
Oh, he's so cute
Is that so?
That's right
Pikachu. Nice to meet you!
Whoa~!
Pikachu, the electric mouse Pokémon
They are rather shy
People should be carefull when handling them
Should have said that first
Yeah, you should have left earlier
Anyway, here's what you'll need
Pokédex and monster balls
Thanks alo...
t~
Ma-ma-ma
Mo-mo-n Monster Ball
Good, good, Satoshi, do
your best, do your best, Satoshi
mamma
It's your own fault for being late
But well, goodbye for
a while, I've prepared travel gear
I really have to look after you until the last moment
Here, shoes and jeans,
shirt's and underwear...
Food at home was a disaster
So, I bought instant food
Rubber gloves, for cooking,
string, for hanging the laundry
That’s enough, you're so over-the-top
Let’s save it for when I become the
ultimate Pokémon Trainer
And I come back to town
You might be right
That's your Pokémon?
Yep! That’s my Pokémon
Ah…
I'm gonna catch all the Pokémon
with this Pikachu
Don’t Pokémon normally go into their monster balls?
Why doesn’t this one?
Oh yeah
Alright, Pikachu, get in
Oh
What?
No...
Kuh...
Well, you're on good terms,
playing catch, aren't you?
eh... Yes
Pikachu and I
are friends, right?
But...
Oh?
That is one strange Pokémon
Strange?
At least his
rubber gloves are going to help.
How come?
Rubber conducts electricity.
Ah, I see...
Make sure you change into your pajamas
every night...
ye- yeah
ah...
Pikachu, are you
going to continue in this state forever?
Do you hate me?
I like you alot
After all, you're the
Pokémon that I need to look after
Wouldn't it be nice if you
listened to me for a little while?
Huh?
Ah... you have teeth,
you’re not toothless
You don't want to talk?
But a Pokémon is a Pokémon—
Aren’t you supposed to go
into your Monster Ball?
It's written
in this Pokédex, too.
The Pokémon kept by humans are
It's usually inside
a Monster Ball
See?
However, there are exceptions to
it, some Pokémon hate small spaces
I get it!
Then let's get along
Let's stop this too
Come on, shake hands
You dont want to?
uh…
Oh?
It's Poppo
Poppo, Sky Pokémon
Among the flying Pokémon, it has the
kindest personality and is the easiest to catch.
An ideal test for beginner
Pokémon Trainers to catch
Got it!
Alright, Pikachu,
go! Let's catch that
Won't you help me?
No matter what?
Understood. That's
right! That's fine!
Alright, if you wont help, it's up to me then.
Who is it?
Pikachu
That's right, he declares that I
am to all the Pokémon of the world
I decided,
the greatest Pokémon master, that's me
catching a Poppo, that’s simple
Monster Ball, go!
Alright!
Ah…
(poppo) po poppo
Oh why...
To catch Pokémon,
normally, you have to make
Pokémon fight each other
I know, but...
But I will do it
Oh?
That's it, Pikachu!
Stay still.
There's nothing to be afraid of
Huh?
Oh, hello
Forgive me now!
Huh?  What's this?
Oh~!
Aw
What was that?
Poppo's Specialty technique: Sand Storm,
followed by a sand attack
Sand?
that's alot different from Poppo on the clock
Ah!  Koratta!
Damn
Forest Pokémon, Koratta,
likes hard foods such as, nuts and cheese
Hey, this isn't a
forest, isn't it a field?
Occasionally they apear in forests and
go after careless travellers' food
Hey, what do you mean careless?
Forgive me!
All right, this time I’ll do it
I did it!
Who are you?
Onisuzume.
Unlike Poppo, it has a violent temper.
They tend to attack humans and other Pokémon
Ahh!
Wait a minute, Onisuzume,
I was the one who threw the stone!
It tends to burn with hostility toward
Pokémon that are kept by humans.
you did it
Ah run away?
Do your best, Pikachu,
I'll definitely save you!
Didn't i just say I'll protect you?
Stop it, Onisuzume!
alright! Let's go
Huh?
Ahhh!
This reaction... could it be the big one?
Huh?
Wait... are you, human?
Ah, what a terrible injury.
Thank you
Why does it look like this?
Poor thing
It's my fault... isn't it?
Don't mess around,
we have to treat it quickly
Near here
They'll treat you at the center
in Tokiwa City Hurry up!
there's a hospital?
One for Pokémon
Ah... so which way
is Tokiwa City?
Over there!
They’re coming, we have to run
Hey!
I'm gonna borrow this
That's my bike!
I'll return it someday!
Goodness
Hang in there,
Tokiwa City, we'll be there soon
Pi... Pikachu
Pikachu, hang in there
Pikachu, get in here
I know you hate going in it
But if you're in there,
I might be able to save you.
Come on, get in, leave the rest to me
You dont know who you’re dealing with
I'm Satoshi of Masara Town
I'm gonna be a Pokémon
master, the best in the world
I wont loose to the likes of you
I’ll stop you all in one shot
Pikachu, get in... your Monster Ball
Are you in?
Come on, Onisuzume!
You risked all that... for me
Who is that?
No data
There are still unknown Pokémon in this world
This is just the beginning of the Pokémon story
Pocket Monsters, Pokémon for short
In front of the boy, Satoshi and Pikachu—
The mysteries and adventures of
the magnificent Pokémon world await
…But now Satoshi and Pikachu are ragged.
Is light waiting for them tomorrow? Or darkness?
What is the future you want?
Dont miss it next time... alright?
(Satoshi) I'm Satoshi
(Satoshi) I managed to get rid of a
large flock of Spur-headed Sparrows, but—
Pikachu got seriously injured
(Satoshi) If I had it cured at the
Pokémon Center in Tokiwa City—
Team Rocket's gang attacked
her, aiming for her Pokémon.
(Satoshi) Even if I fight him,
my Pikachu is under treatment...
(Satoshi) Ah, what should he do!
(Satoshi) Next time "Pocket
Monsters" "Taiketsu! Pokémon Center!"
(Satoshi) This next time
is the time to get Pokémon!